<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Nikesh Maharjan Blog RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Personal blog | Nikesh Maharjan]]></description><link>https://nikeshmhr.github.io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:49:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello, World!!! Welcome to my blog, where I have the pleasure of introducing myself, a software engineer with a keen interest in web…]]></description><link>https://nikeshmhr.github.io/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://nikeshmhr.github.io/hello-world/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 15:17:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hello, World!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my blog, where I have the pleasure of introducing myself, a software engineer with a keen interest in web application security.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a software engineer, I bring a wealth of knowledge and experience in developing and maintaining web applications. However, what sets me apart is my fascination with web application security, a crucial aspect of modern-day development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of my blogging journey is to document my understanding of various topics related to technology and security, and to share insights and valuable information with readers interested in similar fields. Through my blog, I aim to simplify complex concepts and provide readers with actionable advice to protect their web applications from malicious attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today’s world, where the internet is an integral part of our daily lives, web application security has become a critical issue. From preventing data breaches to ensuring secure online transactions, the role of security in web development cannot be understated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re a software engineer or a cybersecurity enthusiast, stay tuned for some exciting and informative blog posts from me. I look forward to sharing my knowledge and learning from my readers along the way.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>